{"data":[{"question":"Can you know when Rachael ___?","a":"will arrive","b":"arrives","c":"would arrive","d":"had arrived","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple future: express the idea of a general prediction about the future ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"My younger sister ___ the choir ___ last month.","a":"has joined, since","b":"has joined, in","c":"joined, in","d":"joined, on","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Simple past tense: express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past (in last month). Sometimes, the speaker may not actually mention the specific time, but they do have one specific time in mind.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"I ___ to work, only to find out that it was a holiday.","a":"hurried","b":"was hurrying","c":"had hurried","d":"have hurried","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Simple past tense (same tense with verb \"was\")\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"Milton was so interested in the novel that he ___ it for a long time without taking a rest.","a":"read","b":"had read","c":"would have read","d":"was reading","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple past tense (same tense with verb \"was\")","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"From the 1910s to the 1950s Hollywood ___ the film center of the world.","a":"was","b":"has been","c":"had been","d":"was being","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The Simple Past can be used with a duration which starts and stops in the past.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"It _________ a long time before I decide to study abroad.","a":"has been","b":"is","c":"will have been","d":"will be","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Simple future: express the idea of a general prediction about the future","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"I must admit that this condition _________ better than it was formerly.","a":"is","b":"be","c":"has been","d":"was","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple present tense (same tense with verb \" admit\")","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"The teacher told the pupils that the earth ___ round.","a":"was","b":"were","c":"is","d":"would be","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Simple present tense: The Simple Present can also indicate the speaker believes that a fact was true before, is true now, and will be true in the future. It is not important if the speaker is correct about the fact. It is also used to make generalizations about people or things.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"As soon as Rose ___ how to use the computer, the boss ___ her a higher position.","a":"will learn, will have got","b":"is learning, will get","c":"has learned, will get","d":"learns, will be getting","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense: We use the Present Perfect to say that an action happened at an unspecified time before now \n- Simple future: express the idea of a general prediction about the future ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"Mr. Tang visited Taipei 101 before _________ for Hong Kong.","a":"he leaves","b":"he would leave","c":"he left","d":"he had left","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Simple past tense:We use the Simple Past to list a series of completed actions in the past","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"}]}